export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "Who is the GOD of cricket?",
        options:[ "DHONI", "VIRAT", "TENDULKAR", "LARA"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the best finisher of cricket?",
        options:["POLLARD", "DHONI", "BEN STOCKS", "PANDYA"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: " Which country has won the most Cricket World Cups?",
        options: ["AUSTRAILIA", "INDIA", "ENGLAND", "SOUTH AFRICA"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: " Which team won the inaugural ICC Cricket World Cup in 1975?",
        options: ["INDIA", "WEST INDIES", "PAKISTAN", "ENGLAND"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: " Which player has the most centuries in Cricket World Cup history? ",
        options: ["VIRAT", "TENDULKAR ", "ROHIT", "SANGAKARA"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: " Who is the highest run-scorer in the World Cup 2023?",
        options: ["RACHIN RAVINDRA", "VIRAT", "ROHIT", "HEAD"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: " Who took the most wickets in ICC men’s world cup 2023?",
        options: ["BUMRAH", "ZHAMPA", "STARC", "SHAMI"],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question: " Who won the ICC Men’s ODI world cup 2023?",
        options: ["INDIA", "WEST INDIES", "AUSTRALIA", "ENGLAND"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: " Chennai Super Kings lifted the Trophy of IPL 2018 for third time by defeating?",
        options: ["HYDRABAD", "MUMBAI", "BENGLURU", "KOLKATTA"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: " Top runs scorer of IPL?",
        options: ["WARNER", "GAYLE", "ROHIT", "VIRAT"],
        answer:4
    },
    
];